Hello friends, today we will discuss the
travel insurance policy of SBI Chief General Insurance.
SBI's
travel insurance policy can only be
taken for business, official, or holiday purposes.
So, let's discuss
who is eligible for this policy.
Any Indian citizen or foreign
national working in India
can purchase this policy. The
age limit for this policy is from six to
600. This policy has some good
positive features, which we will discuss first.
You do
n't need any kind of medical test before taking this policy.
This policy provides you cover of 500,000 US dollars. There is no
room rent
limit or room type mentioned anywhere in this policy. This means
your hospitalization will not depend on the room rent. So,
this is a good feature.
Next, this policy
provides you with an automatic extension of seven days. This
also helps in case your tiffin gets lost due to public transport issues. So
friends, this
policy is available in two plans: single
leg plan and multi plan.  111 is
for those people who are not frequent travellers and have to
visit only once
and Single 111 is valid for ATS,
however you can extend it for a maximum of 27 days.
Multi 111 is for one year
and this policy is also renewable.
Friends, in Single 111 you have to keep one
more thing in mind that
you have to travel within the fourth day of buying the policy
and from the day you travel,
your policy is considered to start from that day. So
friends, let us discuss
what all is there in it. The coverage in both the categories is
exactly the same. So
first of all let us discuss what all is there in it regarding medical expenses.
Friends, whenever we
take a travel insurance policy,
our first target is that if anything happens to
us through any illness or design,
then we will get maximum coverage. This
policy will cover you for medical expenses, related
business expenses, injury or accidental cases.
If you have any expenses, then
it will be completely waived off by the police.
It also covers dental services up
to $225. Apart from this,
if you are hospitalized for
more than a day, then this policy also offers you
shifted toe alarms according to the ward from the second day.
Next, its
coverage of personal accident cover is that if
you suffer
personal
injury, stillbirth or death due to any accident, then this
policy pays you a fixed sum insured i.e.
amount. Apart from all this, the
policy provides a travel support cover
which is quite comprehensive, such as
loss object practice. If your
check balance in an international airline gets
misplaced or lost, then
this policy reimburses you the cost of the valuable items in that bag.
Apart from this, if the
cost of any item is being lost, then you have to
show the return to the insurance company
that if your check package is delayed in the
destination country, you will have to pay
your check in on an Indian international flight when the check has been done
but your bad test on arrival is
more than twelve hours.  If your journey gets delayed,
you get Rs 210 per hour
so that you can purchase your valuable
items or documents.
Next Fiscal Reform Passport: If
your passport gets misplaced or lost due to any reason, then
you are covered at a high reasonable amount to arrange a new passport or alternative
document, so
that you
can arrange the document. Next cover
is Trip Cancellation Curtailment and Delay.
If your trip gets cancelled due to any reason
or your trip gets cancelled
or delayed, then you are covered
at a reasonable amount, in which many times your
accommodation sizes or your ticket
charges are increased.
Next cover is Personal
Liability. In personal liability, if
you cause any third party damage
in your country, then this policy
reverses its cost at that place.
Next cover is Friends, Homework
Gallery Insurance. This policy is an additional cover.
This policy provides you burglary insurance for your house in India.  It
provides
emergency cash
advance. Many times you have an
emergency gas requirement, so the
service provider of the insurance company can
also provide you emergency cash,
provided your local contact
in India provides his security.
Next, hijack cover: This is
included in almost all travel policies nowadays.
Bail bond:
If you are injured due to a car accident, the
insurance company
also arranges for your bail. Next, gifts for
all in one: If you achieve the all in one target, then
this policy also reimburses you the cost of the celebrations.
Friends, travel insurance policy
is quite different from your normal health insurance policy. Travel insurance policy
covers only those of your daily needs
who require urgent medical attention.
Normally, it is covered only
in this where existing businesses are
covered after the time limit.
These system pages are never covered in the travel insurance policy.
Apart from this, friends, if you have a medical  Why are
travel advice orders or even
visits to a doctor for a routine physical examination not directly included in your travel
insurance policy?